You bought a minivan?!
(Howard:)It's for the baby,
and I didn't buy it.
(Howard:)The dealer
loaned it to me
(Howard:)for a 24-hour test drive.
(Raj:)Though we did ding up the back
pretty good with the crib,
(Raj:)so you might have
bought a minivan.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to drive that.
It's such a mom car.
(Howard:)The guy at the dealership said
(Howard:)they're not just
for moms anymore.
(Raj:)Then again,
(Raj:)he did think
you were my husband.
(Bernadette:)They thought it
at the ultrasound.
(Bernadette:)Why not at the car dealership?
(Leonard:)Never been on this side
of the table before.
(Leonard:)I feel powerful.
(Penny:)Really?
(Penny:)I feel like I'm selling candy so
our team can get new uniforms.
Okay, so it's $4.75
for a signed black-and-white
and $9.95 for a color.
(Penny:)Right. Why not five
and ten bucks?
(Leonard:)Well, I brought my moneymaker.
Let me shake it.
(Penny:)Hey, that guy's
looking over here.
(Leonard:)Oh. You think
he's your first autograph?
(Penny:)I don't know. Be cool.
He's coming. He's coming.